

GABRIEL CHIPAYA

WEB DEVELOPER

CAREER OVERVIEW

I am a software developer with experience in mobile/web application design, and development. I am proficient in ES6 modern Javascript, React Js which is a JavaScript library for building user interfaces for web Apps and React Native for building cross-platform mobile apps as well as nodejs/expressjs for the backend.

KEY COMPETENCIES

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind
- React, React Native, NextJs
- Nodels, Expressls
- Mongodb, MySql
- UX/UI Design
- Application Development
- Project Management
- End to End Testing
- Process Optimization

CONTACT ME AT:

Email: gabechipaya@gmail.com Phone: +260 979 788911

github: https://github.com/GABE400?

tab=repositories

Address: Lusaka, Zambia

WORK EXPERIENCE SUMMARY

Web Developer

Visionary Technologies Enterprise | Jan 2022 - present

- Collaborate with designers and other developers to launch web applications
- Write efficient, well-designed code and maintain software documentation

Voluntary Work as a Live Streamer

Revival Fire Missions | July 2020 - present

- Streamed Videos Live using V-Mix Software
- Did some graphic designs using photoshop

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

UNIVERSITY OF GREENWICH



Bachelor of Science (Hons) in computing | Aug 2020 - Dec 2021

- BSc with Honours in Computing
- Took advanced courses on Human-Computer Interaction Design, Requirements Management and mobile application design, and development
- Participated in enterprise system projects

ZCAS UNIVERSITY | NCC Education

NCC Diploma in computing | Feb 2016 - Dec 2019

- Advanced Diploma in Computing
- Specialized in software development
 - eni.
- Database Design and Development
- Agile Development
- Software Development Techniques
- Computer Systems





WORK REFERENCES

Abel Zulu

Head of the media team, Revival Fire Missions Phone: +260 97 7439535

Usana Zulu

CEO, Visionary Technologies Enterprise Email: visionarytechnologiesent@gmail.com

Phone: +260 97 1557763